# **TAMRYN WHITE**

Sheffield South Yorkshire | 07854600132 | tamrynwhite22@gmail.com

I am a motivated, enthusiastic, and reliable individual who can interact effectively at all organisational levels and as a team player or individual. I am seeking an opportunity to apply the skills I have learnt from university in a professional setting, which I hope to pursue a career within. My goal is to develop my skills by working for a company that will challenge me to succeed. The Knowledge I have gained throughout the university will assist me in further developing myself through the right guidance given the opportunity.

## **Skills Summary**

### **Skills**

#### Communication

As a Student Representative, I gathered student opinions and experiences during the semester, as feedback to the university and module leaders. This allowed me to strengthen my communication amongst the students at Sheffield Hallam University, as I would prepare questions to ask, actively listen and lead a discussion. When giving the feedback to module leaders I gave constructive yet balanced viewpoints on behalf of my peers as well as my own opinions as a student.

My internship was conducted remotely which meant I had to communicate with my manager via Zoom, this was something I became accustomed to during the last year at university as all our learning had moved online. I had learnt to use and communicate and present online which gave me some confidence in my abilities.

### Organisation/time management

Towards the end of my first university year, I had multiple assignments with similar deadlines. I had to complete a 3,000-word market research report, as well as a self-reflection essay. This required me to plan and prioritise my time to complete my given tasks to a high standard. I managed to submit both my assignments on time and receive a 2.1 grade on my module.

As a student representative, I was able to improve my time management and organisational skills, while in my final year of university, I had to gather student data using Google Forms to complete the other assignments from my modules, for

example, multiple reports. I managed to prioritise my time effectively and produce high-quality work on time and receive 1st-2.1 grades.

### **Teamwork**

In my modules I would often have to work in groups for projects, an example of this is in my innovation and creativity module, our team created a product concept and had to create a strategy and launch a presentation for it. This involved various meetings to collaborate on ideas and work on the project. As a result of the teamwork, we were able to deliver a successful presentation and achieve 1st grade.

## **Problem-Solving**

This skill has been developing throughout my time at university. In the marketing in a global context module, I was given a task that required me to analyse and conduct research on a single malt Whisky business's current position and recommend a potential new market for its expansion, I conducted a report strategic plan to ensure a successful transition into the recommended market. As a result, I achieved the 1st grade in the module.

As a student representative problem-solving was a skill that I worked on, gathering feedback, and collaborating with the module leaders on how to tackle the issues and come up with resolutions to the problems that the students encountered.

Certifications

Microsoft Office Specialist: Excel Associate 2019
Microsoft Certified Azure Al fundamentals
Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamentals
Microsoft Certified Azure Data Fundamentals

Education

**Birmingham City University** 

Data Science and Cloud Software Course Nov 2022 – April 2023

# Sheffield Hallam university

## **MSc Computing**

Jan 2024 - Jan 25

# **BA Hons Business and Marketing 2.1**

2018-2021

## All Saints Catholic High School

### A level 2018

- Business Studies C
- Religious Studies C
- English Literature D

## GCSE 2016

10 GCSE (A-C) Including English, Maths, Science and ECDL (IT)

# Experience

### **Flannels**

Temporary Stockholm Assistant | November 2021 - February 2022

- I processed new deliveries to ensure new stock was ready for the shop floor.
- I Organised a stock room to make access to clothing easier.
- I Ensured customer satisfaction by delivering the desired items to them.

### **Bolster Solutions**

Digital Marketing Assistant (internship) | June -August 2021

- I designed a digital marketing strategy to gain new clients and increase traffic to the company website.
- I created engaging content based on the digital technology for the company website, in the form of blogpost to boost traffic to the website.
- I conducted market research to find the most suitable segments for target marketing
- Set up KPI on Google Analytics to track conversion rates and click-through rates of the website content

# **Sports Direct**

Temporary sales assistant | November 2016- January 2017

- I drove sales by advising customers on different shoes, training equipment and clothes.
- I guaranteed that my assigned section of the store assigned to me was organised.
- I operated as a cashier putting through transactions.
- I acted with co-workers to deliver customers their shoes.

**Awards and Acknowledgements** 

Student representative